{
  "title": "PBL of Hepatology",
  "questions": [
    {
      "stem": "In a Case of Acute liver failure to test the Synthetic function of the liver We request?",
      "options": [
        "ALT",
        "Ammonia level",
        "PT, INR",
        "Bilirubin Total and direct"
      ],
      "correct": 2
    },
    {
      "stem": "All of the following is from the baseline investigation of the liver except:",
      "options": [
        "ALT",
        "Albumin",
        "AST",
        "succinyle acetone"
      ],
      "correct": 3
    },
    {
      "stem": "ALT is used to assess:",
      "options": [
        "Liver cell injury",
        "Synthetic function",
        "Excretory",
        "Metabolic function"
      ],
      "correct": 0
    },
    {
      "stem": "From the Consequences of Cholestasis?",
      "options": [
        "colored stool",
        "fat malabsorption",
        "vitamin B deficiency",
        "Pruritis"
      ],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "stem": "Anatomic Causes of cholestasis include:",
      "options": [
        "Niemann Pick disease",
        "Cholelithiasis",
        "Choledochal cyst",
        "Cystic Fibrosis"
      ],
      "correct": 2
    },
    {
      "stem": "Hepatitis markers for diagnosis of chronic hepatitis B infection in a thalassemic multi-transfused 10-year-old child are:",
      "options": [
        "HBsAg -ve, antiHBc IgG +ve, antiHBs +ve",
        "HBsAg +ve, antiHBc IgG +ve, antiHBs -ve",
        "HBsAg +ve, antiHBc IgG -ve, antiHBs -ve",
        "HBsAg -ve, antiHBc IgG -ve, antiHBs +ve"
      ],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "stem": "Male infant with cholostatic jaundice, what is the most important vitamin to give",
      "options": [
        "A",
        "K",
        "E",
        "D"
      ],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "stem": "A child was vaccinated against HIB which marker is positive",
      "options": [
        "HBC Ag",
        "HBe Ag",
        "HBs Ag",
        "HBs AB"
      ],
      "correct": 3
    },
    {
      "stem": "A kid with jaundice, fever , vomiting, What is the next thing to do?",
      "options": [
        "ultrasound",
        "HBs Ag",
        "HAV IGM",
        "HCV PCR"
      ],
      "correct": 2
    },
    {
      "stem": "in Wilson disease which is low",
      "options": [
        "Albumin",
        "ferritin",
        "trasfrrin",
        "Curulopalsmin"
      ],
      "correct": 3
    },
    {
      "stem": "Immunological evidence of hepatitis B is the presence of:",
      "options": [
        "Hepatitis B Core antibodies",
        "Hepatitis B Core antigen",
        "Hepatitis B surface antibodies",
        "Hepatitis B surface antigen"
      ],
      "correct": 2
    },
    {
      "stem": "Reye's syndrome is caused by using salicylates (Aspirin) on treatment of severe viral infection in the child age group:",
      "options": [
        "True",
        "False"
      ],
      "correct": 0
    },
    {
      "stem": "the most common cause of neonatal (infantile) cholestasis is",
      "options": [
        "Galactosemia",
        "alpha1 anti tyrpsin defeciency",
        "Neonatal idiopathic hepatitis",
        "extra hepatic biliary atresia"
      ],
      "correct": 2
    },
    {
      "stem": "which of the following is Not agenetic Cause of Neonatal Cholestasis?",
      "options": [
        "Allagile Syndrome",
        "Galactosemia",
        "Extra Hepatic Biliary atresia",
        "Recurrent Benign Cholestasis"
      ],
      "correct": 2
    },
    {
      "stem": "All are Causes of Cerebral edema in Acute Liver cell failure",
      "options": [
        "Hyponatremia",
        "Hypoalbuminemia",
        "Cerebral vasodilation",
        "Hypokalemia"
      ],
      "correct": 3
    },
    {
      "stem": "The most important diagnostic sign of portal hypertension is...",
      "options": [
        "Jaundice",
        "pallor, Severe",
        "splenomegaly"
      ],
      "correct": 2
    },
    {
      "stem": "Anti Hepat. B. Core Ab IgG +ve in which condition:",
      "options": [
        "Vaccine",
        "Recent infection",
        "chronic infection",
        "immune"
      ],
      "correct": 2
    }
  ]
}
